helpost.com 2018-08-12

# Helpost

Privacy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Helpost (“we”, “us”, “ours”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users signing up to Helpost (each, a “User”) of the helpost.com website (the “Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Helpost. 

(That, helpost.com and Helpost Softwares Private Limited can be used interchangeably) 

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site without providing their personal identification information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can refuse to supply personally identification information, except however, it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include but not limited to, the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If such an option is enabled please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

How we use collected information

Helpost may collect and use Users personal identification information for the following purposes: 

\- To improve customer service   
Information you provide, helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

– To personalize user experience   
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.

– To improve our site   
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 

– To share your information with third parties   
We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.

– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature s  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

– To send periodic emails   
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Sharing your personal information 

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Changes to this privacy policy

Helpost has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will notifiy on our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Helpost Softwares Pvt. Ltd.  
http://www.helpost.com  
#152, Friends Colony,  
Khanna,Punjab-141401  
+919888839993  

Last update on January 12, 2015
